Let's pray for the viewers.
I release you from the pain of the past!
Be released from the pain of the past!
Pain of the past is the cause of unforgiveness.
It is the cause of bitterness, the cause of envy and jealousy, the cause of hatred.
Be released, in the name of Jesus!
Every unclean spirit operating in your life, be released, in the name of Jesus!
Open your lips and begin to release yourself, in the name of Jesus, by the authority given to you.
Every unclean spirit operating in your life, operating in your career, operating in your marriage.
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
These unclean spirits are the cause of pressure and tension.
They are spirit beings that cause pressure and tension.
Be released, in the name of Jesus!
Say to yourself, "I am released!"
Believe that!
I can't hear you!
[I am released!]
Viewers all over the world, I can't hear you.
In the name of Jesus!
I can see you being released!
Take it; believe it.
This is the Word of God.
I can see you being released!
Whatever satan might have used to connect you to himself, I see you being released!
I see it being broken!
Whatever satan might have used to connect you to himself,
to connect your business to himself, to connect your career to himself,
to connect your marriage to himself, to connect your health to himself,
I see it being broken!
Yes, I can see chains falling!
I can see them being broken!
Every chain satan might have used, I can see them being broken!
Whatever chain satan might have used, I can see them being broken!
Confess this; confess your freedom now.
Chains have been broken!
In Jesus Christ's name!
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
TT: Unknown
RV: Mel Flowers 01/04/2019